Take your medicine, dear.
The rain smells nice.
Once it's over,
shall we go for a walk?
Take your medicine, then we'll go.
Inspector.
Forensics is on their way, almost here.
Has this crime scene been photographed?
Yep, all done, sir.
Phii Pong!
It's Phii Pong! Narong is Phii Pong!
If they locked him up,
Shaman Sak wouldn't be dead!
This is revenge.
Shaman Sak knew!
He knew Narong is Phii Pong!
Don't worry.
Everything will work itself out.
DELUSION
The case you made,
for Mued's killer was pretty strong.
Until your suspect was killed, too.
Yes, sir. But maybe he didn't act alone.
Someone else knows about the body.
Everyone…
knows about that kid.
Ever since the Phii Pong case years ago.
And the cases you
found in other provinces.
Plan of attack?
Sounds like we'll close one case,
but open a new one.
I'd rather you didn't complicate
things with cases from other provinces.
When the evidence doesn't
seem to be linked at all.
We have to figure out
who killed Sak and that's…
enough of a headache for us already.
I just need more time, sir.
I'll give you that
but don't let this become a thing
that blows up on the news.
The messier things get,
the harder it is to finish the job.
Here.
But, do me a favor and be careful, okay?
Yes, sir.
They can't release the body.
Till the autopsy.
Now what, Mom?
I'm done waiting.
Let's go ahead…
with the funeral.
I'm the only family he's got.
How many days, Mom?
Three days… is enough.
Did Dad go out that night?
Oh, you--
You think your dad did this?
I was just asking.
Can we go now?
I'll need to head off
to the temple to sort things out.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Wan?
It's Supattra, Mr. Yote's attorney.
Yes.
I'm calling about the mediation date.
Your attorney hasn't
gotten back to us yet.
I've just had a lot on.
I'll get back to you when I can.
Well, please don't take too long.
I don't want this to have to go to court.
We don't want to have to bring up
what happened between your father and Aim.
Do we?
Inspector.
Look at this.
The neighbor and Saeng's boy
filmed this last night.
He heard Grandpa Narong shouting.
Ghosts in the forest! Don't go in!
- There are ghosts here!
- Where is he now?
With the duty officer.
Can you keep a copy of this?
Already done.
Thank you.
ANUPONG'S PHOTO
PACHARA JUNSAYPUN
PORNCHAI JAMROON
SAK SONGSIPHAN
Hello there, ma'am.
Counsellor.
Ah, my condolences.
I'm sure the police will
do everything they can.
To find out who did this,
and catch them soon.
Please take this for the funeral.
The Shaman lived all by himself.
It's a big part of land.
He must have had some
other relatives though, right?
No.
I guess the land is all
yours in that case.
A blessing and a curse.
I don't really know
about those things, sir.
Well, I'm here to deliver
the land mortgage agreement to you.
He mortgaged it with me
for over 200,000 baht.
And he paid back almost nothing.
Now, the interest is almost double that.
I'll round it down to 350,000 baht.
Pay this back
and I can give you back your land.
I understand it's a bad situation.
You didn't even spend the money
and you're left with the debt.
We all have to follow
the law though, right?
I don't want this to…
end up in court.
We're like a family here.
So--
Inspector?
Not here.
- Sergeant.
- Oh! Yes, sir?
If we disregard the teeth,
could it be the same killer?
Uh…
Got this for you.
Hmm.
Roughly speaking,
looks like this hut's within
the boundaries of Narong's property.
71 YEARS OLD, MEMORY IMPAIRMENT, SUSPECT
Where are you going?
The temple, to make merit.
Why are you in black then?
People don't wear black to make merit.
Won't be long.
I'll bring something to eat.
Ghosts in the forest! Don't go in!
If he needs to pee,
or walk around,
I let him out at night
for ten minutes or so.
After that, he's tied up till morning.
You can just tie him up by yourself?
Oh, we can tie him up when he's sleeping,
or really out of it, from the mat.
Hmm.
Or maybe you're lying.
Which means I can't help him.
Help him?
Whatever for?
Were you aware of enemies
your brother had?
To end up dead, like Mued.
You think it was my husband?
Then arrest him.
Mom… don't. Don't.
Whatever else you need…
you go ask him, I'm busy.
That's all right.
I'll let him rest.
But I'm counting on you to keep him here.
Don't let him wander off.
Uncle Sak's case is still open.
Don't want people calling him a ghost.
Okay, Mom, let's go inside,
I'll take you to the temple.
She was lying.
Her lip trembled, see that?
LAWYER SUPATTRA:
IF YOU CANNOT SCHEDULE THE MEDIATION,
MR. YOTE WILL FILE FOR DIVORCE
AND PRESS CHARGES AGAINST MR. NARONG.
- Mosquitos?
- Mmm.
Ah, here. Mm?
There.
You look upset.
Something wrong?
I'm fine.
Beat the boss in your game?
Huh?
The one with the slashes.
- I did.
- Oh!
Did you get mad?
No way!
Mmm.
Do you miss me yet?
Mmm-hmm.
Mom.
Hmm?
I got into a Bangkok school.
Dad said he wants me to start
middle of next term.
Oh.
Well, I guess I should
look for a job in Bangkok, hmm?
You being away…
I think I might die.
I'll tell Dad to wait
till you get a job first.
Then I'll go.
Well, Bangkok's pretty nice.
Good facilities,
and great sights.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Should we get some ice cream then? Huh?
Then I'll drop you back.
- Good?
- Yeah.
Mom!
Mom.
We're not really getting
ice cream, are we?
If you're going to Grandpa's house,
I don't wanna come.
Why not, Aim?
Because we're poor?
Or is it something else?
What did you tell your Dad?
Aim, tell me what happened.
I didn't tell.
Aim.
Please don't lie.
Don't lie to me!
Aim, come on!
What did you say?
Huh?
Grandpa pushed me into the water.
He-- He wasn't making any sense!
It was scary!
Aim…
Why didn't you tell the police?
Why didn't you tell me this before? Huh?
So Dad wouldn't get mad at you!
Aim…
Don't cry now. You did nothing wrong.
I'm sorry for getting angry.
Now, let's go back to Dad, hmm?
Before he worries.
See you at your red belt test, okay?
Mmm.
See you then, little boy.
See you then.
Why is he here?
BORN 14 MAY 1962
DIED 18 NOVEMBER 2026
NEVER TO WAKE
NEVER TO RETURN
For you.
Oh, thank you.
Take your dad home.
Who knows when this will end.
I'll get someone to give me a lift.
Well go on, go home.
Thanks so much.
No, of course.
Your house is right next door,
we're family, right?
Narong has new pills.
He's really improved.
And he didn't kill Mued.
Didn't the police tell you that?
They did.
So, stop sticking your nose
in our business.
You worry about your own family.
Stressed out about family?
Well, you don't need to be.
Your family's rolling in it.
That sounds crazy. Make your point.
So this is a surprise?
Your family owns lots of land.
Even Uncle Sak's house
is yours.
The Phii Pong forest as well.
And now your dad is sick
and your uncle's dead.
Your mom might be the only one who knows.
Seriously?
If you think they did it, arrest them.
But don't ask me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Her daughter…
and this is the first I've heard of it.
You think your brother
knows about the land?
Don't know.
Okay, I'm done.
If anything changes…
I'll get in touch if I happen
to need anything else, okay?
That's all.
Keep it down.
He's sleeping.
- What are you looking for?
- The deeds.
Or anything that can be sold.
This is what you want.
LAND TITLE DEED
Why did you give Dad's land to Uncle Sak?
Didn't think about your own grandkids?
Mind your business.
Why do you care now?
You never…
even thought to tell me?
Were you saving it all for Wat?
You know nothing, shut your mouth.
Don't meddle.
I don't want to!
But when something goes wrong…
it's me!
I have to clean up your shit!
So go back to your house!
We're fine.
Why do you hate me so much?
Hmm?
The only reason I married
that fucking asshole
was so I could save
my family from being poor!
Did you never think
about what I had to sacrifice?
Everything I've done has been for you!
And I've never gotten…
a single thank you.
So what?
Nobody's ever thanked me, either.
Well, thank you.
Setting the cases
in other provinces aside,
the suspects right now
are all members of Narong's family.
The first Phii Pong murder happened
on Narong's property.
Near a hut the family claim
they don't know the owner of.
That same year,
Narong passed this land over
to Sak.
Pannee's older brother.
But with no payment, huh?
Here's what I think.
The first Phii Pong murder,
and Mued's murder,
I think might have been the same killer.
But I think, Sak…
was murdered by someone else.
As for all the murders
where teeth are missing…
which resemble the Phii Pong cases,
but happened in other provinces…
whoever that killer is,
must have some connection to this family.
Nee?
Nee.
Why are you awake?
Is Sak here somewhere?
Mmm-hmm.
Tell him to go home.
He's got enough.
We've given so much.
He's got your land.
What else does he want?
We need to stop, Pannee.
I've had enough.
Come on!
Pa!
You called the police right?
No? Why?
I…
I told you!
What if someone really dies?
What do we do?
Wait! Pa!
Pa!
I'm so sorry, kid!
Pa! Pa, come on! Stop!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry…
Hey Sak, the rake now.
Let's stop,
before anyone else dies.
Let's talk to the police.
And, we won't have to lie anymore.
I'm tired.
Who?
Who's doing it now?
If you don't give it to me,
I'll go to the police,
let them arrest us all.
Hmm.
Paw.
He's gone into the forest again!
You've got to go bring him back!
What?
No! No no!
He can't go in there!
We can't let him go in there!
But, don't be scared!
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Ghosts in the forest! Don't go in!
There are ghosts in the forest!
Don't go in there!
Pa!
Get away!
- Let me go!
- Go away!
Get him away!
Let me deal with this!
Ma?
What are you doing?
Let's get out of here!
Let's go now!
You don't know! All the things I've done
for you!
- Phii Pong! You're the ghost!
- Yeah!
I am! I am! It's always been me!
Now get out, you two leave!
Come on, Pa!
I'm sorry.
It hurts!
Nee!
Help me.